但其实我的口音是乡下农民口音
but I actually speak with the accent of a peasant.
总之  我今早在巡逻时
Anyway, I walked my beat this morning,
特意用俄语跟几个人聊天
and I spoke to several people in Russian.
他们都觉得我很厉害  对我敞开心扉
They were so impressed, they opened up to me.
-我获得了好几条有用的线索  -太好啦
- I got a number of useful tips. - All right.
这都是因为我强迫你做了无趣的事
All because I made you do something tedious.
是单调而已  别毁了这气氛
Monotonous. Don't ruin this.
谢谢各位前来参加希契科克的离婚派对
Thanks for coming out to Hitchcock's divorce party.
你知道你又弄了个基佬蛋糕吧
You know you got another gay cake, right?
什么  不可能
What? No way.
上面写的是"兄弟  兄弟  兄弟"
It says "Boys! Boys! Boys!" on it.
因为我们是好兄弟啊
Because we're the boys.
各位  我想明白我和安娜之间是哪里出了问题了
Guys, I figured out what went wrong between Anna and me.
是因为我的工作  我是个工作狂
My job. I'm a workaholic!
不再是了
Not anymore.